( vigorous gamelan music )
( dramatic ominous chants )
( suspenseful gamelan music )
I 'm surprised , that a pretty girl like you ,
would be interested in learning black magic .
Well , I 'm just curious .
I 'm thinking that maybe one day ,
I can write a book about it
and tell it to the world .
Before I came here ,
I did some research in Africa on voodoo .
It 's a subject which has always fascinated me .
I hope you 'll be able to help me
in my research here , Hendra .
Hmm . Yeah .
I know a little about the Leak magic .
It was said , the most primitive
but also the most dangerous .
A Leak master can change his form at will ,
and do anything he wishes ,
like sand animal , or a tree ,
or even another person .
It 's kind of weird , isn 't it ?
It 's really unbelievable .
( vigorous gamelan music )
( characters converse in foreign language )
They say , one can kill by using the Leak magic .
But the thing about it is no murder
can be proven if one uses this magic .
( dramatic gamelan music )
( characters converse in foreign language )
( men shriek bizarrely )
Now , do you agree to help me with this ?
Hendra , oh , come on .
I need your help , you 've gotta help me .
Alright .
I 'll try my best to help you .
But you know I can 't promise you anything .
Thanks a lot .
Thank you , Hendra .
( ominous suspenseful music )
Hmm .
Cathy .
Time to go home now .
And you ?
Where are you going ?
I 'm going home too .
And tomorrow , we 'll get an early start , okay ?
( loud engine roaring )
( birds chirp )
They 're right .
It doesn 't have any smell at all .
So you 've heard the story , too ?
Yes , I heard it from your friends ,
Suryani and Jogja .
But that was the extent of his information .
He couldn 't tell me who started it .
Well , there 's still an awful lot
of mystery in Bali , you know ?
I also find it hard to believe sometimes .
And that 's why , Hendra , I 'm so interested in
this Leak magic .
I want to find out all the secrets of
this unusual branch of black magic .
And the only possible way to do that
would be to learn it myself .
The same way , I learned voodoo ,
the black magic of Africa .
It 's going to be a fascinating book when
it 's finished .
[ Hendra ] I 'm sure , it will be .
Cathy , voodoo or any other black magic
is nothing compare to this Leak magic .
According to what I 've heard ,
the Leak is the most powerful of all magic .
Hendra , but tell me , do you believe in the Leak ?
Or is it just nonsense ?
I believe in the supernatural and also black magic .
But I also think that , in a way ,
its reputation is over dramatized a bit .
Then , I see you do believe in the Leak , don 't you ?
I have to believe in it , Cathy .
We need a clear mind to learn it , right ?
But I 'm afraid my mind can 't be clear when
I 'm next to a beautiful girl .
( chuckles )
Mahendra , perhaps you and I are the only two people
who 've ever dared to kiss besides all these old skeletons
and skulls .
Because of you .
Let 's go , pretty or the ghosts will get mad .
( chuckles )
( tense dramatic music )
Oh .
You ! You really gave me a fright !
I brought some big news for you .
Oh yeah ?
What 's the big news ?
You know the friend I told you about .
He just told me that he managed to find
a Leak master who would talk to you soon .
Thanks a lot , Hendra .
So tell me then , when are we gonna get
the chance to see him ?
No hurry .
Just be patient .
Right . I 'll try to be patient .
( animals croak )
Well , Cathy , this is the place we 've agreed upon .
Oh , but it 's so quiet , it 's like a graveyard .
Yeah , but Cathy , remember we 're now
confronting forces which are very far beyond
our everyday 's experiences .
We can expect anything to happen now .
( lighting crashes )
( hard rain pours )
Does this mean the Leak master is coming ?
Yeah . Now we just gotta wait for him to appear .
( ominous dramatic music )
Hey , I spotted something !
Huh ? Where is it then ?
See , there ?
You 're right . I see it !
That heap of brush seems to be shivering .
It looks like it , doesn 't it ?
But that 's not a heap of brush , Hendra .
Is that it , do you think ?
Could be .
It 's strange . Look at it .
Why do you think it 's turning round and around like that ?
Maybe it wants to make sure that
its presence not being seen by
anybody else unless it has to .
What 's the next step now ?
What should we do , Hendra ?
( loud maniacal laugh )
Cathy .
I think I can recognize that laugh .
A terrible laugher , that 's a sign
of the most horrible clan of them all .
What 's that ?
Yeah . The Leak laughter is their special trademark .
And appearance is always preceded by the laughter .
What 's most the dangerous about them is that they can kill !
( loud evil cackles )
Who is that ?
The master certainly knows that we 're here now , Cathy .
Let 's go over .
( creepy dark music )
So , who are you then ?
My name is Mahendra .
I arranged yesterday to come here and see you .
Hmmm .
But who is that young girl with you and
what is her business ?
Well , in fact , she 's the one who wanted to meet you .
Hmmph .
Has she ?
And why should you come along as well ?
Uh , I 'm just escorting her .
She 's a foreigner here .
Ah .
The girl is very lovely .
What is her name ?
And where did she come from ?
Catherine Kean from the USA .
And where is that ?
Very far away .
Hmmph .
Tell me why you wanted to meet me .
'Cause I 'm interested in learning
the most powerful magic that exists today .
( laughs dramatically )
Well now , I know the world 's most powerful black magic .
And I 'm the greatest master .
That we are the most terrifying magic there is .
The Leak magic !
( laughs evilly )
I will accept this young girl starting tomorrow ,
she 'll be my disciple !
Alright , then now , the terms !
But how do we know that tomorrow ,
it will be you ?
Not someone posing as you ?
We don 't know you .
Hmmph .
You want to see my face .
( laughs dramatically )
Alright then .
But you might look at it carefully .
You 'll never forget this face .
( laughs maniacally )
This is my face that you see tonight , young man .
But you must remember one thing .
My face will change everytime I make an appearance .
No one will recognize me .
As my face is never the same , it 's different each time !
Oh , that 's right .
I 've heard of your Western custom .
When people say good bye ,
they shake each other 's hand , like
this !
That 's right .
We will part now .
I 've gotta leave , so good bye !
Let us shake hands , Catherine .
( laughs maniacally )
Ugh !
( strange ominous music )
( wolves howl )
( creepy haunting music )
[ Cathy ] It 's a terrible smell here .
( cackles loudly )
[ Leak Master ] Pretty brave .
I 've been waiting for you .
Who are you ?
[ Leak Master ] Who am I ?
( laughs dramatically )
I 'm the queen of Leak .
Whom you met last night .
Where are you , master ?
[ Leak Queen ] I 'm just behind the bushes .
But you don 't need to see me ,
do you understand ?
I do .
[ Leak Queen ] Have you brought those things
I asked you to bring ?
Alright . Listen carefully to me .
Put the jewels on the palm of the girl 's hand .
Now , tell her to stretch her hand out and
I will take them from her hands .
You see now I know that you can be trusted .
Now , I need blood .
I 'm very thirsty !
I 've walked a long way !
( strange ominous music )
Mmm . Good . Delicious .
This is good blood .
Alright .
Now tell me young lady ,
are you ready for the first lesson ?
Hmmm . Good .
Good .
Now I need you to take off your skirt .
What are you gonna do ?
[ Leak Queen ] Don 't you argue with me .
She must take off her skirt !
Because I need to write a few mantras of Leak
on her skin .
Is there another way ?
This girl doesn 't want to be a Leak forever !
[ Leak Queen ] I know that !
I 'm not going to hurt her .
This is only to pass on some magic knowledge to her .
She 'll only have a few scratches
on the outer layer of her skin .
Once the outer skin is peeled off ,
the magic will disappear .
Just tell her to do what I say !
Hmmm ?
I need to write the magic spell
in the secret place .
And no one can see it ,
otherwise it 's no good .
Understand ?
( ominous dark music )
( strange crackling scratches )
We need to do this tonight .
Now , no one will see the spell there .
( loud groans )
This is a cloth full of black magic words .
Take it !
Tomorrow night , the girl must come again .
But be sure she wears a tapi and remember ,
to bring the cloth with her !
The tapi is an undergarment .
And it 's worn with all of our local traditional dresses .
[ Leak Queen ] Uh-huh .
And young man , you do not need to come with her tomorrow .
She must come alone .
I 'm not disturbing anything , am I ?
So why can 't I come tomorrow ?
[ Leak Queen ] You are too curious , young man .
You ask about things that you shouldn 't know about .
I suspect you .
My instinct tells me that you are a dangerous and
unreliable person .
So do what I say !
Go now !
( owl hoots )
Here .
What is it , Hendra ?
Just open it .
And then you 'll find out .
Oh .
Mahendra .
Really , you 're much too kind .
You 're always so generous , aren 't you ?
You remember even the little things .
What can I say except to thank you , Hendra .
It 's kind of you . I appreciate it .
Don 't need to thank me , Cathy .
It was really nothing at all .
You know , I promised to help you .
As much as I could , I 'm just trying to keep my word .
[ Man ] Excuse me , sir .
Here are your drinks .
Ah . Put it down there .
[ Man ] Is that all , sir ?
Yes , thanks .
Hey Cathy .
Now remember .
Before you wear the batik ,
don 't forget the tapi , you must wear as your undergarment .
So try the tapi before you go .
Alright . Don 't worry .
Let 's go inside .
This drawing is vague .
A lot of jumbled pictures .
I suppose it 's like this .
So that no one can understand it .
Well , it is interesting .
But I 'm afraid it 's all complete mumbo jumbo to me .
Maybe we 'll know after we see the Queen tonight .
( chuckles lightly )
There must be a meaning to all of it .
If we can understand it , it will be better .
Don 't forget tonight you 'll be alone .
She said I can 't come with you .
Yeah , but , there is another way to do it .
What do you mean ?
Well , as you know , last night ,
the Queen of the Leak drew a spell on my thigh .
[ Hendra ] Yes . And ?
I was just wondering if maybe you could read it .
But ?
Hendra . Come on .
I 'm sure you want to know its secret too , don 't you ?
Yeah .
I 'm just trying to figure it out right now .
You can come closer .
So you can read it clearly .
Hurry up , Hendra , before anyone comes here .
( strange mesmerizing music )
Can you understand it , Hendra ?
No .
Oh tell me what do you think it is , then ?
Is it different to the one in the amulet ?
Well most of it is different .
I haven 't seen anything like this before .
But a small part of it is quite similar .
Cathy .
Hmm ?
I think I can recognize this .
Oh yeah ?
Uh . But the sound .
Le .
Le ak .
Ak .
Leak . Leak !
Oh , that 's a start .
Then you 're on the right track .
Now , what else can you see , Hendra ?
A picture she drew on the front of your thigh ,
it must be a sign .
That means you 're now officially accepted as
a new student of the Leak .
( giggles )
Take a closer look .
Tell me what else you can figure out from it ?
Uh . I think that 's about it .
I can 't understand the rest of it .
And this is where it says , um , uh .
Oh , that 's enough .
Oh okay .
I guess I 'd better get ready to go out soon .
( strange animals cry )
( ground collapses )
( eerie animals cry )
( loud maniacal laughter )
( roars loudly )
( suspenseful percussion music )
( laugh together excitedly )
( odd frightening music )
It was really frightening .
Can you guess what we did , last night ?
Um . Tell me .
Well , Hendra .
You 'd never believe what happened .
Hmm ?
I will soon be a master of the Leak .
This is really hard to believe .
You ? You , a master of the Leak ?
That 's right .
So does that mean you can
change into anything you want to ?
Of course .
Last night , at midnight ,
everything was exactly as we had arranged it to be .
I was there with the Leak Queen .
And then , suddenly .
( strange disturbing music )
( flesh protrudes loudly )
( grunts crudely )
That 's the story , uncle .
So tell me , is it true ?
That another spell exists
that is strong enough to fight
this Leak spell ?
( sighs heavily )
Of course , there is .
If there wasn 't .
Then , the world would 've been taken over
by the Leak and everybody would be under
their evil power .
And so how do we recite this spell then ?
Mmm .
Actually , it is quite easy .
The first thing that one should do is
to recite the holy words , Trisandi .
( chants in foreign language )
Now let 's get back to what we were saying earlier .
Once you have learned to say the Trisandi ,
the thing you must do after that is
to recite the other mantras .
( eerie haunting music )
I think you 're old enough to accept the mantras
but remember one thing , Hendra .
You mustn 't fool around with these mantras
and you mustn 't tell anybody about them .
Where did you get all these mantras , uncle ?
I got them from our forebear , who 's also my uncle
as far as I know he 's stolen them
from the house of the great Leak master .
Unfortunately , he was discovered .
And the Leak master finally managed to track him down .
A duel ensued .
My uncle was not familiar with the mantras then .
And so he was unable to use them
to fight against the Leak master .
So .
He was very lucky indeed to survive .
So my uncle was seriously injured .
While he was recuperating ,
he managed to learn the techniques and
passed them on to me .
So has the mantra ever been used
to fight against Leak ?
Yeah .
Many times and with good results .
( ominous dark music )
Hendra .
This little dagger you see here is great power .
It 's yours now .
Take it and it 'll increase your power .
Go on , take it .
So it means that you can communicate using telepathy .
And you don 't have to say anything to each other ?
Yeah .
And also , you 're able to think like another form of life ?
Is that right ?
Yeah .
And I only realize it now that I can do it .
That ball of fire that you told me you had destroyed
could be yourself .
The fire goes out means someone has died .
That is , a life 's being destroyed .
Means a human being has died somewhere .
Are you saying that I 've killed another human being ?
That 's right .
( gasps )
Hendra .
This is turning into the most horrible nightmare !
You mustn 't worry , Cathy .
But , Hendra .
This would mean that I 'm now a murderer !
Yeah .
But it wasn 't your doing !
Oh .
( groans painfully )
What 's up ?
Huh ?
I don 't know .
My stomach 's aching .
And my heart , feels like it 's going to burst !
It could be from last night .
Go lie down .
( whines softly )
Hey , I 'll call a doctor for you , okay ?
No . Don 't call a doctor .
You don 't look very well , Cathy .
And we don 't know , you may get worse
and it could be dangerous .
Let me call a doctor .
I might get a little worse .
But it won 't be dangerous .
No good leaving it ,
you must treat it before it gets worse .
Let me call a doctor .
Hendra , only the Leak would be able to cure this .
But then , I can 't go to her now .
The sun is real high . It 's noon time .
So that 's impossible .
I must wait until later .
I 'll be alright .
She told me to go back again
to the graveyard tonight .
For she 's going to cure my illness
and after that , she 'll teach me
the remaining lessons , okay ?
Okay . Up to you .
Now , you have a rest .
I 've gotta go into town this afternoon .
There 's some business there I really have to attend to .
Hendra .
By tomorrow ,
tomorrow morning , I 'll be the old Cathy again .
I 'll be the same old girl that you used to know .
I hope tonight that can happen .
Catherine Kean should always be Catherine Kean .
( giggles softly )
Oh . Thank you .
You 're the best thing that ever happened to me .
If I was in your condition , I don 't think I could laugh .
It 's all because of you , Hendra .
( gentle romantic music )
( ominous dark music )
( lightning crashes )
( loud maniacal laughter )
Catherine , I gave you invaluable lessons
in the black art .
And now ,
it 's time for you to pay !
I 'm your mistress , you have to obey my orders at all times .
And now ,
I will have to borrow your head for a short time .
And then I will attain total power .
( groans )
( painful groans )
[ Man in Brown Shirt ] It 's been a long time .
[ Man in Grey Shirt ] Yeah , I 'm worried .
( groans loudly )
Hey , it 's alright , the baby will be here soon .
There , there .
( cries painfully )
[ Man in Brown ] You know , she seems to be having
a lot of trouble .
( screams )
( loud crash )
( grunts heavily )
( yelps painfully )
( disturbing scary music )
Rose !
( ominous dark music )
No !
I succeeded !
I succeeded finally in moving your head !
And utilizing it !
Now I need the new blood to make me younger
and even stronger !
( laughs maniacally )
Your illness is cured .
On the lessons you 've received so far ,
ought to have been enough .
If you still wish to carry on ,
I will certainly continue to accept you as my disciple .
If you 'd like to stop ,
perhaps later .
I have now learned enough .
Thank you for everything you 've taught me and
for all the lessons .
I do appreciate it .
Hmmph .
( eerie ominous music )
( laughs dramatically )
You can 't just walk away like that , young lady .
It 's not so easy .
I will never let you get away !
( ominous dramatic music )
( lightning crashes )
( strange eerie music )
( dramatic transformation music )
( slithering softly )
( gags )
Cathy !
( dramatic eccentric music )
( vomits violently )
Cathy ! What 's the matter with you ?
I really don 't know .
All I can recall is
that I saw the Leak Queen .
And we laughed a lot together .
And then ,
we went to a strange place
where I saw plenty of delicious-looking delicacies ,
and I ate a lot of the things that were on the table .
Perhaps it was the food , last night .
But it made you so sick now .
( strange ominous music )
[ Voiceover ] So , here we are .
Finally we meet .
After so long .
[ Leak Queen ] Come and fight your master !
( indistinguishable groans )
( loud screams )
( loud explosion )
( laughs maniacally )
( strange grunting )
( indistinguishable groans )
( powerful explosion )
( laughs maniacally )
So now .
There you are , the Leak Queen ,
has finally defeated her enemies !
( suspenseful dramatic music )
[ Hendra ] As you see ,
you got a separate entrance to your room .
That way , you can come and go as you like .
Thanks a lot , Hendra .
I like this place .
It 's really very peaceful here .
It 's very good too , it lets me concentrate on my book
without any interruptions .
I hope I 'll be able to finish it soon .
I want you to know that
so far Mahendra has never been wrong
in his selections !
( giggles )
Hendra !
Cathy !
I do care a lot about you , Hendra .
I know you do .
I think perhaps I shouldn 't allow you to go back to the USA .
( sweet romantic music )
[ Man ] Excuse me .
My boss told me to deliver this receipt .
Oh yeah ?
If there 's anything you need ,
you can just call us ,
we will be very glad to help you .
Thanks a lot . It 's very kind of you .
I 'll be so lonely .
I had no idea you had to sail so soon .
Really .
You work hard for your money , don 't you ?
Uh .
Tell me how long is it gonna be ?
Only for two days .
Mmmm .
I 'll surely miss you , Hendra .
I 'll be missing you too , Cathy .
Although we 've only met a short time ago ,
I feel as if I 've known you for years .
You know that without you here ,
I 'll be sad and depressed .
( dramatic ominous music )
( groans uncomfortably )
( gasps )
( loud maniacal laughter )
( dramatic horrifying music )
( loud scream )
Ugh !
( eerie disturbing music )
Must have been a dream .
Perhaps I was just thinking too much about my book .
My mouth . And the blood .
I guess I bit my lip .
( strange discontent music )
( suspenseful dramatic music )
According to the information we 've got ,
it seems that this thing was a flying head .
The funny thing was ,
this flying head had light-colored hair .
The Leak so far only seems interested in
newborn babies for their blood ,
according to relatives of the dead .
This is very serious !
We must try to find a solution
to stop this demon right now !
Yeah .
I 'm afraid this world has become
a very evil place , these days .
Many have forgotten the Almighty God
and His teachings to us .
There are a lot of men who are greedy .
Many who are after power to control
and dominate others .
Black magic is a poison in our society .
We have got to try to exorcise it .
We have got to try to kill it .
And pull out the roots .
In order to get rid of it ,
we 'll have to pray for help from the Almighty .
The great Lord really was there , has also
given us power to protect our people
from all evil sickness .
And naturally , it 's up to us to make use of this gift .
I 'm all for what Machesse said .
The goal of this meeting today is to work out a way
to put an end to all of this .
After years of peace and quiet , comes a disaster .
The Leak magician needs to consume three lives .
To complete her power .
Up to now , she 's already taken two lives .
That means she 'll need to find one more .
And then her power will be complete .
Now .
I 'd like to handle this thing quickly .
I will need to go and meditate .
And pray to seek the help of Almighty God .
Please , excuse me .
( laughs maniacally )
Why are you so surprised ?
I am your teacher .
Huh ?
I already had the lessons .
I 've finished now .
Pretty , you have had all of your lessons .
But you still have not paid me .
Well , how much do you want , then ?
I 'm not interested in money , my lovely .
I don 't want money .
I want hot , fresh blood and you can go out and
get it for me !
Alright . Tomorrow .
I 'll go and get it .
I can 't wait any longer .
I want you to get it right now !
It 's so late .
Where can I find it at this hour ?
Well , that is easy .
I just need to borrow your head for a moment .
( gasps )
You can 't !
I 've used your head twice before and
you 've always obeyed me !
Now you must go again .
One last time .
And after you have done it ,
I will release you .
You can leave , then .
'Cause you see , after this one last time ,
then my power will be complete .
My body will live forever !
( laughs maniacally )
I could stay on forever .
( laughs dramatically )
Don 't !
( eerie dramatic music )
( airplane jet roars )
( intense ominous music )
( indistinct angry shouting )
( dramatic suspenseful music )
( hiss )
Oh my God , it 's you !
Mahendra !
What the hell are you doing here , then ?
Go and have a look and I 'll explain everything !
( eerie suspenseful music )
It 's all clear . I think I know everything .
I must admit .
I never would have thought that
this thing will go as far as this .
Yeah , but don 't worry .
Maybe Catherine 's being used by
some evil supernatural forces now .
Maybe .
Uncle , if you help me , perhaps
I can get Catherine back on the right track again ,
do you think so ?
It 's much too late now , Hendra .
I 'm afraid no one can separate her now
from her evil teacher .
You mean that it 's all over then ?
Uncle , but I do love her very much !
But many innocent lives are being lost .
And you know very well yourself
it 's all because of people practicing black magic .
I 'm sorry to tell you
we can 't afford to have any more deaths !
But , please , uncle !
Many people have lost their lives
because of this black magician .
And I 'm gonna stop it no matter what !
Now , please !
Please let me help her !
No , Mahendra . You can 't go or you 'll destroy everything !
That girl isn 't the same anymore .
She has now become Satan 's prisoner !
( ominous dramatic music )
( angry grunts )
[ Machesse ] Mahendra .
[ Hendra ] Yes , uncle ?
[ Machesse ] Come with me .
I 'd like you to help me pray on this grave
for three nights continuously ,
do you think you can do that ?
For what reason ?
'Cause Cathy 's body 's gonna rise again .
As her head 's no longer attached to her body .
And then , if that happens , I 'm afraid that
all of us are going to be placed in the gravest danger .
The body has to be buried
according to the Balinese tradition .
Catherine 's no longer the girl you know .
She 's Satan 's prisoner .
She 's Satan 's executioner .
Remember , she 'll kill anyone in her way .
We 've got to try and stop the body joining the head .
If she succeeds in reuniting her body with her head ,
we 'll never control her .
I guess it 's all my fault that
Catherine has become like this now .
It 's my fault .
Because I started it .
It 's true when they say that
failure always gives us the courage
to face reality .
You must move on .
You have your future ahead of you .
You mustn 't let this ruin your life .
You 're right .
Uncle , I should have listened to
what you said to me before .
Yeah .
You go now and I 'll join you tonight .
( suspenseful mournful music )
Hendra .
( sorrowful romantic music )
Hendra , I love you a lot .
Please promise me .
Hendra , you 've really got to help me this time .
I 'm in trouble .
You 've got to get my body out of the grave .
You got to help me for our sake .
I love you .
( gasps )
( intense dramatic music )
( screams )
Tell me . What 's the meaning of that dream , uncle ?
I think that it signifies her return .
So you see , the next three days is very important .
We 've got to prevent her head from joining her body .
Otherwise , she 'll become invincible then
there 'll be nothing we can do about it .
Why should she appear to me in a dream ?
The Leak Queen has sent Catherine back
to try to influence you , Hendra .
If you are weak ,
well then ,
she 'd have succeeded .
And you 'd have gone to the grave and helped them .
We still don 't know if we 'll win .
Is that right ?
( yawns )
Mmmm .
I 'm very sleepy , should we take turns to watch the grave ?
You two go take a nap .
We 'll watch first .
Do you remember the dagger I gave you ?
Do you have it with you , Hendra ?
Yeah , I have .
I brought it with me tonight .
Mmm . That 's good .
Perhaps we 'll need to use it later .
( strange eerie music )
( growls angrily )
( screams )
( loud explosion )
( laughs maniacally )
Hey , idiot !
There 's no one to interfere with my affairs !
So you 're the one who 's behind all this .
I know you .
Aren 't you satisfied with all these deaths ?
( laughs maniacally )
I 'm glad you still remember me .
It 's true , you have defeated me once before .
But that was a long time ago .
I warn you . Don 't try anything stupid .
I don 't care what it will have cost !
I 'll destroy you and your evil kind !
You wanna destroy me ?
Hmmph !
Just you go ahead and try !
( groans )
You idiot !
So you still possess the power , don 't you ?
But not for very long , you hear me ?
Yaaaah !
( groans strenuously )
( strange eerie music )
Yeaaah !
( loud explosion )
( laughs maniacally )
Oh , so come on !
Fight me , old man !
( laughs maniacally )
( electrifying punches )
( groans painfully )
Hey evil witch !
Come on and fight me then !
If you still love me , Hendra .
Go on , drop the dagger .
Drop it .
( dramatic intense music )
[ Machesse ] Mahendra ! You mustn 't drop the dagger !
( laughs evilly )
I 've destroyed my old rival !
I got revenge !
( laughs maniacally )
( stern hits )
( yelps painfully )
( wolf howls )
Maya ? Why ? Why did you do it ?
It 's because I still love you , Hendra .
Although you left me for another woman , Hendra .
I still love you very much .
Maya .
Maya , I 'm sorry .
Maya ?
Maya !
( eerie dramatic music )
( groans painfully )
( lightning crashes )
Oh .
Oh I see . It 's you again .
I Gusti Oka , the greatest one of all !
So , you again .
I 've come here to lend a hand to my nephew .
Though I was late for my brother .
One thing 's for sure , his death won 't be for nothing .
So , you want to avenge him !
Now it won 't be so easy , Oka .
Show me what you can do !
Alright . So let 's start .
( loud clashes )
( screams painfully )
Hmmph . Oka . You are good .
More powerful than before , I see .
But don 't think I 'm not as strong
once I regain my lost energy !
I tell you .
I will surely get you sooner or later !
You can just mark what I say !
( groans )
( eerie suspenseful music )
( fire roars )
( electricity crackles )
( grunts angrily )
Alright then , I must fight you , Oka !
We shall soon see who is going to die !
Today is going to be your head or mine !
( screams )
( slashes dagger violently )
( stabs forcefully )
( laughs maniacally )
( loud explosion )
( double explosions )
( laughs evilly )
Hyaaaa !
( powerful explosion )
( slashes forcefully )
( gasps painfully )
Gyaa !
( chuckles maniacally )
Huh ? !
( rooster crows )
( screams painfully )
( flesh sizzles slowly )
( groans unintelligibly )
( gasps )
( sorrowful eerie music )